First rule, you get 12 hours.
Second, follow my lead and change nothing.
Just stick to the script.
Third.
I know, past and future.
Must remain untouched.
Let's discuss the mission.
You're to grab financial data from Treda Games
before their third quarter report is released the day after tomorrow.
A female corpse was found in the river last night.
According to the police, the deceased was employed in the financial department...
You're all trash and need to be slaughtered.
You'll pay, I promise.
I'll kill every last one of you!
Hey, Chanbin!
The page about the seventh victim isn't in the file.
I thought I'd killed her.
Then, I heard someone else screaming.
Liu Min couldn't have killed that woman.
We have the proof.
It'd be impossible.
Last night at 1.30, somebody broke into Zhu Shanxan's place,
and then he attacked her.
Tomorrow at this time, find the real me.
Figure out his M.O.
Give him some hints as to who we are,
and make him play by our rules.
I'll see you very soon.
And when that time comes,
don't you dare cheat again.
If I did change something,
how many lives would be affected?
So it's true.
There was a witness after all.
Interesting.
What did you just say?
What if...
If...
You mean was...
You're another one of his friends, eh?
You...
Can possess people, too?
Liu Kuan.
I'm sorry.
Everything is going to be different now.
Shaolin!
Death isn't something any one of us can change.
Liu Kuan!
The best we can do...
is accepted.
So please,
don't let this be another burden for you to carry.
Liu Kuan!